<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IELTS Mock Test</string>
    <string name="listening_button">Listening</string>
    <string name="reading_button">Reading</string>
    <string name="writing_button">Writing</string>
    <string name="speaking_button">Speaking</string>
    <string name="exam_button">Exam</string>

    <string-array name="matching_sentence_ending">
        <item></item>
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>C</item>
        <item>D</item>
        <item>E</item>
        <item>F</item>
        <item>G</item>
        <item>H</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="matching_statements">
        <item></item>
        <item>YES</item>
        <item>NO</item>
        <item>NOT GIVEN</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="matching_feature_list">
        <item></item>
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>C</item>
        <item>D</item>
        <item>E</item>
        <item>F</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="matching_information_list">
        <item></item>
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>C</item>
        <item>D</item>
        <item>E</item>
        <item>F</item>
        <item>G</item>
        <item>H</item>
        <item>I</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="q_1">1. Andrea is feeling happy because</string>
    <string name="q_1_a_1">she\'s seen Harry.</string>
    <string name="q_1_a_2">she\'s finished her exams.</string>
    <string name="q_1_a_3">she can sleep well.</string>

    <string name="q_2">2. What is Harry\'s problem?</string>
    <string name="q_2_a_1">He doesn\'t want to sell his things.</string>
    <string name="q_2_a_2">He needs to decide what to do with his possession.</string>
    <string name="q_2_a_3">He wants to take everything to England.</string>

    <string name="q_3">3. Where is Harry going to advertise his books for sale?</string>
    <string name="q_3_a_1">In the university bookshop.</string>
    <string name="q_3_a_2">In the student newspaper.</string>
    <string name="q_3_a_3">In the economics department.</string>

    <string name="q_4">1. In a Japanese pagoda, the shinbashira</string>
    <string name="q_4_a_1">bears the full weight of the building.</string>
    <string name="q_4_a_2">bends under pressure like a tree.</string>
    <string name="q_4_a_3">connects the floors with the foundations.</string>

    <string name="q_5">2. Shuzo Ishida performs experiments in order to</string>
    <string name="q_5_a_1">improve skyscraper design.</string>
    <string name="q_5_a_2">be able to build new pagodas.</string>
    <string name="q_5_a_3">learn about the dynamics of pagodas.</string>

    <string name="testing">This page will provide Android ScrollView with fixed header and footer layout example.
        When the number of lines of body content will be more, there will be scroll line.
        In our example there will be a header which will always be fixed at the top of mobile screen and a footer that will always be fixed at the bottom of the screen.
        The body content have scroll view with full body view.
        Find the complete example.
        This page will provide Android ScrollView with fixed header and footer layout example.
        When the number of lines of body content will be more, there will be scroll line.
        In our example there will be a header which will always be fixed at the top of mobile screen and a footer that will always be fixed at the bottom of the screen.
        The body content have scroll view with full body view.
        Find the complete example.
    This page will provide Android ScrollView with fixed header and footer layout example.
        When the number of lines of body content will be more, there will be scroll line.
        In our example there will be a header which will always be fixed at the top of mobile screen and a footer that will always be fixed at the bottom of the screen.
        The body content have scroll view with full body view.
        Find the complete example.
    This page will provide Android ScrollView with fixed header and footer layout example.
        When the number of lines of body content will be more, there will be scroll line.
        In our example there will be a header which will always be fixed at the top of mobile screen and a footer that will always be fixed at the bottom of the screen.
        The body content have scroll view with full body view.
        Find the complete example.
    This page will provide Android ScrollView with fixed header and footer layout example.
        When the number of lines of body content will be more, there will be scroll line.
        In our example there will be a header which will always be fixed at the top of mobile screen and a footer that will always be fixed at the bottom of the screen.
        The body content have scroll view with full body view.
        Find the complete example.</string>

    <string name="reading">
        Passage: \n
        In a land swept by typhoons and shaken by earthquakes,
        how have Japans tallest and seemingly flimsiest old buildings - 500 or so wooden pagodas - remained standing for centuries?
        Records show that only two have collapsed during the past 1400 years.
        Those that have disappeared were destroyed by fire as a result of lightning or civil war.
        The disastrous Hanshin earthquake in 1995 killed 6,400 people, toppled elevated highways, flattened office blocks and devastated the port area of Kobe.
        Yet it left the magnificent five-storey pagoda at the Toji temple in nearby Kyoto unscathed, though it levelled a number of buildings in the neighbourhood.
    </string>

    <string name="passage_1">
        You should spend about 20 minutes on <b>questions 1-13,</b> which are based on
        Reading Passage 1 on the following pages.\n
        A song on the brain \n
        A \n
        Everyone knows the situation where you can\'t get a Song out of your head. You hear a pop song on the radio - or
        even just read the song\'s title - and it haunts you for hours, playing over and over in your mind until you\'re heartily
        sick of it. The condition now even has a medical name - \'Song-in-head syndrome\'. \n\n
        B \n
        But why does the mind annoy us like this? No one knows for Sure, but it\'s probably because the brain is better at
        holding onto information than it is at knowing what information is important. Roger Chaffin, a psychologist at the
        University of Connecticut says. "It's a manifestation of an aspect of memory which is normally an asset to us, but in
        this instance it can be a nuisance." \n\n
        C \n
        This eager acquisitiveness of the brain may have helped our ancestors remember important information in the past.
        Today, students use it to learn new material, and musicians rely on it to memorise complicated pieces. But when this
        useful function goes awry it can get you stuck on a tune. Unfortunately, superficial pop tunes are, by their very nature,
        more likely to stick than something more inventive. \n\n
        D \n
        The annoying playback probably originates in the auditory cortex. Located at the front of the brain, this region handles
        both listening and playback of music and other sounds. Neuroscientist Robert Zatorre of McGill University in Montreal
        proved this some years ago when he asked volunteers to replay the theme from the TV show Dallas in their heads.
        Brain imaging studies showed that this activated the same region of the auditory cortex as when the people actually
        heard the Song. \n\n
        E \n
        Not every stored musical memory emerges into consciousness, however. The frontal lobe of the brain gets to decide
        which thoughts become conscious and which ones are simply stored away. But it can become fatigued or depressed,
    </string>
</resources>
